- Hola!
Soy dora...
And this is my best friend boots
We're getting ready
for our big gymnastics show...
I get to dance the ribbon dance
with my special rainbow ribbon
will you have me do my ribbons dance of the show
Fantastic!!
Aoh Aoh
that sounds like
swiper the fox.
If You see swiper,
Say swiper
Swiper!
There he is!
Swiper, no...swiping
oh no!!We need to get that Ribbon back
We need just to figure out where is it
let's check map
map says we have to balance free
walk over crocodile lake
trampoline jump through flower garden
and swing on the ring to get to the gym
Wow ,, Fantastic gymnastics
were you help us to find rainbow ribbon so i can do
my ribbon dance of show ,,fantastic
follow us,, let's go
Llegamos we made it to crocodile lake
wow,These crocodiles sure are snappy
we can cross the lake by balancing
on the tree trunks.
it's just like walking balance beam at the gym.
press the arrow keys to walk the tree trunks
en Los troncos...
press space bar to jumb
remember,,only jumb on the on the los troncos
watch out for Los cocodrilos.
we need to jumb on turnks to cross the lake
we need to jumb four tree trunks to cross the lake.
what publing up on  cocodrilo
what publing up indronko or cocodrilo
that wasn't cocodrilo
We need to jump on the trunk
one mopiean.
tow great.
three four almost there.
one more tree trunks to go.
oh cocodrilos,
four mo bian.
we made it.
we cross four tree trunks all to gather.walk through trunks.
now we need trampoline  jumb through flower  garden,gaminouse.
we made it to the flower garden.
we need to trampoline  jumb the flower garden.
so we can find the rainbow ribbon for my ribbon dance
of the big gymnastics show .
will you help us, great.
look for rainbow starts,yeah,,
how to choose the way through the garden
we can hatch them too.
watch out of silly flower.
we need to trampoline jump on the bouncy flower that we get us all the way of cross.
use your mouse click on the taller flower.
mopiean.
watch out for spider.
use your mouse to click on the shortest flower,ring.
whoops!!
thanks of the way  of the flower garden.
weeeee!!
we need to swing on the rings next faminouse.
neaeda,i see the rainbow ribbon.
i can use those rings to swing up and grapp the ribbon
come on boots give me a push.
i swing to the number seven.
the ribbon is in the number nine.
to get to number  nine ,i need to swing higher or lower .
click on an arrow .higher great.
give me anther push boots.
that's it,i swing to the number nine ,nine.
we got my rainbow ribbon .now i can do the ribbon dance.
we have to gym next  so i cane start the big gymnastics show ,
fantastic gymnastics.faminouse.
will you have make really special ribbon dance,,mabian.
click on these buttons to filling our dance movies up here.
filling all  six pieces to put  to gather  a hole dance.
to erase the last dance move  and chose the new one
click the blue undo button.
to watch me perform my special dance click the green done button.
first..
second..
third.
fourth.
fifth.
sixth.
its time to dance .
excellent .thanks for helping do my ribbon dance extra special.
mytriloisa.mytriloisa, we did it ,,noysimose
now we will say ,,fantastic gymnastics.
ready fantastic gymnastics.
click print to print fantastic gymnastics colours by numbers page.
click play again to play fantastic gymnastics adventure again